styleware.eu 2015-12-28

# Privacy Policy

Written by Grigor Mihov      
Wednesday, 07 April 2010 13:56   
  
Privacy Policy of StyleWare is used in order to protect its customers privacy and security of information stored and shared with us through the web site www.styleware.eu. This policy explains clearly how we collect , use and maintain your personal information. By registering and using our site you give consent automatically to use and disclose information if required by law or by state authorities. Unless you agree with any terms below, **you should not use** products or services offered by StyleWare.

StyleWare may collect personal information about you, which will be stored in case of registration in our web site (www.styleware.eu) or its subdomains or by registering for our newsletter. We will require you to enter your name, username and password to be able to login in our website. Apart from that, in case of issuing invoices or other documents, the buyer is obliged to inform us about his/her detailed personal information; such as name, address.

Except the use of your personal data for administrative and analytical purposes, it is allowed to use it in case of some legal actions. Protection and defense of the rights or property of StyleWare are taken into consideration, as well as, merger or other business actions.

If you give permission to send you informative messages, including newsletters about product upgrades, updates, new products/services or discounts available, you have to remember about informing us about changing or updating your e-mail address or other changes you may make. If you are unable to make any changes yourself, we can do it on your request. Also, remember about unsubscribing when you do not want to receive any news messages from us as it is possible to do so.

Information gathered and stored at styleware.eu is fully protected. We do our best to secure data collected and do not disclose to any unauthorized person. All data is restricted to StyleWare employees and external service providers only and they are entitled to use your personal information, however, it is forbidden to misuse this data. If anyone uses classified data in the wrong way, we will take appropriate disciplinary action.

However, we do not take responsibility for data used during PayPal payment as your personal information used there is not registered by our system and has to be protected by PayPal security system.

We need to have consent to disclose your personal information because it is impossible to make any purchase without it. If you do not agree to share this data with us, it will be barely possible to offer you any services/ products.

At any time, you may inform us about not willing to share with us your personal information and disclosing it. However, because of that fact our services offered will be restricted. Apart from that, there are some situations where we are forced to use your personal information despite the fact that you withdraw your consent to disclose your information.

Should the need arise, you would contact us at  [privacy@styleware.eu](mailto:privacy@styleware.eu).
